[narrator] Leol has pursued Morel
into an underground church,
where they will now face off in battle.
[chuckles]
[screams]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
My Tube ability summons the ocean!
[Morel grunts]
[gasps]
[Leol] Well? What do you think
of my big wave? Huh?
Just stay still,
and you'll die even quicker.
[Leol] He's making a boat out of smoke?
I see. You can ride on top of it.
[both grunt]
[Leol] Ha!
Do you really think
that's enough to tame my waves?
Huh. This one is one of my original moves.
[yelling]
Vortex!
[inhaling]
[Morel] Damn it. The current's so strong
I can't tell up from down.
This is bad.
Here goes.
Then finish him with a harpoon from above.
by traveling at the speed of sound.
Take this!
[gasps]
Wait. He disappeared?
Impossible.
The whirlpool
should have kept him trapped.
He had no way to escape.
Ah.
Bastard.
Okay, then. Looks like it's my turn now.
is that your ability
somehow uses the abilities of others.
Or you could be getting all your orders
from somebody else.
[growls]
[Morel] If he's increasing his risk
by limiting his hearing
in order to upgrade his ability,
he shouldn't be able to hear me.
What's the third thing?
Third is your life span.
Tube once belonged to a Hunter I knew
named Grachan, not you.
He was helping to exterminate Chimera Ants
so I suppose you must have defeated him.
And since you stole his ability,
you deserve to die.
[chuckles] I'm only borrowing it.
Only borrowing it, huh? [scoffs]
That's a lowlife thief's excuse,
if I ever heard one.
Huh?
[Leol] I can see that arguing with you
is just a waste of my time.
I'd like to get my hands on his ability,
but defeating him's more important.
No.
He was confident in his lung capacity,
so he can survive for 10,
maybe 20 minutes.
No, wait. It's possible
he could stay underwater for even longer,
-[bubbles popping]
-Huh?
There you are.
Now hold still,
and I'll stab you with my harpoon.
-[bubbles popping]
-Huh?
I get it.
It's possible he could've formed his smoke
into a hose with multiple branches.
That way,
he wouldn't have to reveal his position.
No, it's not.
The bubbles are camouflage.
Did he escape?
I told Welfin and Bloster to stay back
so I could take all the credit.
[gasping, groaning]
My head's spinning, and my chest hurts.
[gasping]
My board's gone!
I'm too unstable to keep it activated.
[straining] Can't move or breathe.
My ability stopped working,
but the water's still here?
Not good.
I let him think he had the advantage
so I could turn the tables on him.
But it looks like the one
who was backed into a corner was me.
Is this it?
Is this the end?
So he was using a hose made of smoke
to send air bubbles everywhere.
It's CO2.
[narrator] Morel used
his immense lung capacity
to suck in the stagnant air
trapped in the church
[Morel] You might not have realized it,
but my attacks began even before yours.
If what he said was true,
Grachan should be getting his ability back
right about now.
[Bizeff snoring]
[Palm] I'll be free to move around
for a few hours.
In that time,
I have to see them with my own eyes.
I've watched Bizeff's movements
with my crystal ball.
[clanging]
[gasping]
They're close. Right above me.
[gulps]
[breath shaking]
[gasps]
[whimpering]
[people speaking indistinctly]
[groaning]
[gasps]
Oh. You're up. That's good.
You were out for two whole days.
Two days? I need to get going.
Whoa! Just take it easy.
Your wounds still need to heal.
[grunts] But there are things
that I have to do.
Idiot! You were on the verge of death.
You can't just go running off now.
You'll need to rest before--
-[doctor] Ah, look who's awake.
-[Ikalgo] Huh?
How wonderful.
[Killua] Thanks for helping,
but I'll be checking out now.
Not until you pay your bill.
And the total comes to 1.8 million Jenny.
If you can't pay,
then I'll accept body parts instead.
I don't have my wallet with me,
so I'll wire it as soon as I get back.
Do you really think that I'm stupid enough
to take an IOU from you?
[line ringing]
It's 10,000 Jenny for each minute.
Quiet! Just shut up, and go away!
[Gon] Hello?
[Killua] I'll tell you when I see you.
An enemy gave me a little bit of trouble.
I've been in the hospital.
That sucks.
But thanks for calling.
So you're okay, right?
Yeah. Heading back soon.
[Killua] Oh.
[Gon] Let's talk it over
as soon as possible, okay?
[Killua] Sounds good, but, hey,
I need you to send money to an account.
Do that and we can rendezvous later today.
[chuckles]
[Gon] I guess that just leaves Palm.
You mean you haven't
been able to reach her yet?
What about Pitou's En?
With that, she'd be found,
maybe already has.
I imagine that she's down
in the underground hangar.
she won't be able to get out.
[Gon] How's Mr. Knov doing?
He's, uh…
probably done fighting.
But he did manage to plant the exits,
so it hasn't changed our plan.
[stammers]
Right. I'm good to go.
-[door opens]
-[doctor] Okay.
Your payment finally came through.
You're all cleared to leave now,
so get out.
[door opens]
-[Killua] What are you doing?
-Uh…
-Let's go.
-[stammers]
We're gonna go join my friends.
I'll introduce you.
Uh…
But…
[gasps] Uh, wait.
I mean…
Is it really okay?
I mean, I'm just a…
You're sure?
I can go, too?
[Killua] I'm sure!
Well? Are you coming or not?
[Ikalgo] Yeah, I'll go! I'll go with you!
Let's just get one thing straight.
and I end up helping you out,
[Killua] I'm sure that you and I
will be helping each other out
all the time from now on,
It's not worth it.
Killua, I… I'm so happy, I could die!
Wait! What the hell
are you crying about, huh?
'Cause you're doing this
for someone like me.
-[sobbing]
-[sighs] Give me a break.
it's more brutal than what you're used to.
[gasps]
It may seem similar,
but there's a huge difference between
risking your life and throwing it away.
But if you can take
perfect care of your body
and drink poison
that's barely under the lethal dose
without the least hesitation,
you can survive.
Thanks for the warning,
but all I see is paradise.
I'll go, no matter the cost.
I've seen the other side.
I have a connection to it now.
-I know it really exists.
-[closing theme song playing]
And now I know that even someone like me
can go there!
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Killua] Four-three-three-two?
[Gon] Hey, that's my phone number!
[singer singing in Japanese]